AI-Based Environmental Color System in Achieving->[{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99932224, 'word': ' Institute of Industrial Design', 'start': 24, 'end': 54}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99875045, 'word': ' Huaqiao University', 'start': 58, 'end': 76}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9219733, 'word': '.', 'start': 104, 'end': 105}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9994804, 'word': ' Institute of Industrial Design', 'start': 140, 'end': 170}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99880433, 'word': ' Huaqiao University', 'start': 174, 'end': 192}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99806225, 'word': ' City University of Macau', 'start': 201, 'end': 225}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99875134, 'word': ' State Key Laboratory of Subtropical Building Science', 'start': 235, 'end': 287}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9856183, 'word': ' South China University of Technology.', 'start': 289, 'end': 326}]
Automated diabetic retinopathy detection in smartphone-based fundus photography using artificial intelligenceSustainable Urban Development->[{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9993308, 'word': ' DMDSC', 'start': 68, 'end': 73}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9962486, 'word': ' Remidio Fundus', 'start': 154, 'end': 168}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9975572, 'word': ' DMDSC', 'start': 213, 'end': 218}, {'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9978603, 'word': ' Gopalapuram', 'start': 220, 'end': 231}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9738165, 'word': ' ICDR', 'start': 240, 'end': 244}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9903106, 'word': '.', 'start': 252, 'end': 253}, {'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9993343, 'word': ' Kaushal Solanki', 'start': 273, 'end': 288}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9991902, 'word': ' EyeNuk Inc', 'start': 307, 'end': 317}, {'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.9970335, 'word': ' Los Angeles', 'start': 320, 'end': 331}, {'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.99986136, 'word': ' California', 'start': 333, 'end': 343}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9688693, 'word': ' Eye Art', 'start': 440, 'end': 447}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9903106, 'word': '.', 'start': 456, 'end': 457}]
Attention Is All You Need->[{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9998439, 'word': ' Nal Kalchbrenner', 'start': 36, 'end': 52}, {'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.99986655, 'word': ' Stephan Gouws', 'start': 57, 'end': 70}]
A Supervised Approach to Extractive Summarisation of Scientific Papers->[{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99699926, 'word': ' Elsevier', 'start': 34, 'end': 42}]
Artificial Intelligence for Efficient Thermal Comfort Systems Requirements, Current Applications and Future Directions->[{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9998965, 'word': ' Ed Arens', 'start': 65, 'end': 73}]
Meibomian Gland Density: An Effective Evaluation Index ofMeibomian Gland Dysfunction Based on Deep Learning and Transfer Learning->[{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9992676, 'word': ' Jing Ye', 'start': 28, 'end': 35}, {'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.99909365, 'word': ' Xuewen Chen', 'start': 85, 'end': 96}, {'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.99909735, 'word': ' Lu Li', 'start': 98, 'end': 103}, {'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.99838275, 'word': ' Chaoqun Zhang', 'start': 105, 'end': 118}, {'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9990565, 'word': ' Yingyu Mao', 'start': 124, 'end': 134}]
A Review of Fundamental Optimization Approaches and the Role of AI Enabling Technologies in Physical Layer Security->[{'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.94211984, 'word': ' PLS', 'start': 92, 'end': 95}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9486715, 'word': ' PLS', 'start': 230, 'end': 233}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9798284, 'word': ' AI', 'start': 323, 'end': 325}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.939168, 'word': ' PLS', 'start': 360, 'end': 363}, {'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.95335186, 'word': ' PLS', 'start': 484, 'end': 487}]
Recent Applications of Artificial Intelligence from Histopathologic Image-Based Prediction of Microsatellite Instability in Solid Cancers: A Systematic Review->[{'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9906513, 'word': ' Na Jin Kim', 'start': 9, 'end': 19}, {'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.99430853, 'word': ' Ah Reum Kim', 'start': 96, 'end': 107}]
CeCILE - An Artificial Intelligence Based Cell-Detection for the Evaluation of Radiation Effects in Eucaryotic Cells->[{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99790955, 'word': ' Maier Leibnitz Laboratory Munich', 'start': 22, 'end': 54}, {'entity_group': 'PER', 'score': 0.9998471, 'word': ' Thomas Schmid', 'start': 115, 'end': 128}]
Ensuring the Reliability of Virtual Sensors Based on Artificial Intelligence within Vehicle Dynamics Control Systems->[{'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.99462664, 'word': ' Open Access Publication Fund', 'start': 30, 'end': 58}, {'entity_group': 'ORG', 'score': 0.9917304, 'word': ' University of Duisburg-Essen.', 'start': 66, 'end': 95}]
Development of Anticancer Peptides Using Artificial Intelligence and Combinational Therapy for Cancer Therapeutics->[{'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.8714873, 'word': ' Y.I.K.', 'start': 31, 'end': 37}, {'entity_group': 'LOC', 'score': 0.91425455, 'word': '.', 'start': 62, 'end': 63}]
Intelligent Process Automation: An Application in Manufacturing Industry->[{'entity_group': 'MISC', 'score': 0.9952113, 'word': ' IPA', 'start': 215, 'end': 218}]
